question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },

    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Pointers were not used in the original C programming language; they were added later on in C++.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The &quot;Berenstein Bears&quot; is the correct spelling of the educational children&#039;s book "
                 "series&#039; name.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]

